This is a self-portrait, so this is basically me, right?
Okay, I know.
I have an idea.
It looks like something that would be in Stranger Things or something.
Hi, I'm Jenny and I'm going to be sculpting my self-portrait.
I feel like I'm in an art class right now.
I don't think I'm a good sculptor at all.
I am kind of scared to do this.
I'm taking my nails off guys.
I don't think I can sculpt with these.
This is my body.
I'm trying to build my body first and then I want it to the face.
I think my eyes, also because I'm kind of blind.
I can't see well, so I have to like look at myself really close up
in the mirror and then my eyes are there.
It's more of a lifestyle than one era for me.
Everything regarding what I do is to do with my album, my mindset, I'm prepping
my body for my album and what's to come after.
So I think that's what I mean by it's become a lifestyle of mine.
This is really fun.
I wonder if there's a tool to help me.
You need to cut?
Like...
Oh, yeah.
To pet.
I really thought about it, and my answer is, I want to enjoy this life
as a pop star and then think about what to be in my next lifetime.
I like the present moment the best.
I love my job.
What do you love most about it?
That I get to sculpt something in front of 30 people.
Okay, finally time to cut something.
Ah, can I take this Yeah, the shoes.
Then I'm just gonna need to perfect everything.
I think I'm still figuring that out.
I still don't know when to stop.
Yeah, I'm so accustomed to keep going.
And there's still so much on my list that I want to get done.
And I push myself further every time.
So I haven't met my limit yet.
I'm planning like next year, maybe I could start slowing things down.
Being at home is one of my favorite things to do.
I haven't really had time to really like stay home after the pandemic.
so that's something that I want to do more in the future and maybe go
on vacations, stay in bed as long as I want and then watch a movie
and eat something good.
That's all I'm asking for really.
My essentials from my home.
I like to bring my pillow and my blanket with me so I feel as
closely as being at home.
I have a very big luggage that I bring everywhere I go, and it basically
has everything from my house.
I think it's more of a comfort thing.
I'm sure I can buy the same thing, but just the feeling of having something
from home.
I wish I had another darker red.
Can you help?
Wow.
That's a good question.
I'm like the friend in the group that keeps everything not fall out
of places.
They come to me a lot when they need to decide on something or need
help
That that really just came out of nowhere, um, thank you I'll keep it right
here
I don't think so.
I'll try.
Oh, you're really soft.
I can mix it.
That I don't give up.
This is something that I've learned about myself during the
time of working on my album.
think I can say that this journey was easy but every time I had I
faced a new situation or learned anything new I
kind of kept pushing myself to do more in within myself and that's
that's how the album was made so I'm so proud of it and I love
that about me.
Everything was a challenge for me.
This was my very first time working on a solo album, a full album.
I really just ran into brand new things.
I'm making petals right now of a flower, trying to make a red rose.
Did you want to make that?
This is my face.
Oh, that's your face?
Yeah.
I get really distracted when I listen to music.
If I need to be focused, I don't listen to music.
I meditate.
I started doing it a lot more during the pandemic.
And yeah, it became a lifestyle so meditation is a part of my album
a lot of the times i'm most creative when i'm meditating with my own words
and my own expressions because i know it's in a safe place it really just
helps me focus on myself and the stronger and confident you feel about
yourself, like the better version of you appears.
And also there's so many benefits.
I just can't list them all right now, but it was a crucial part of
my album.
I don't have self-doubt.
That's how I got here.
I'm just really clear on what I want and what I like and it can
change over time from learning new things and experiencing new things but I always like
to sorry it's from what I'm making I always like to believe 100%
in the way I think and deal with the consequences I'm so sorry guys am
I like over timing
Okay guys, I am ready to reveal my self-portrait.
In 3, 2, ta-da!
This is who I am right now.
This is how I envision myself with my album, Ruby, coming out.
I am peaceful.
I am zen.
I'm blooming in the ruby red color.
And I'm just sitting there meditating.
This is how I see myself and yeah the back.
I'm just manifesting this.
This is so special.
Thank you Vanity Fair for creating this time.
I had so much fun working with clay today and answering you guys'
questions.